yo yo yo good morning snow peas good
morning comma army come on of us five
there buddy we got some exciting stuff
for you today I can't show you these TVs
there's secret stuff on these TVs um yo
yo that guy look no we got new products
that they're actually kind of excited so
let's give everyone minute to get in
here we'll listen to fan joy to the
world while we wait you guys know this
song called fans right of the world it's
a song about about merch oh yeah so I'm
repping some new merch right now
it's calm a t-shirt $20 right now shop
comma thought I'd check it out okay the
shirt is made from I don't know versus
like $20 right shield for a company no
we are army yeah I wish I could put my
thing on a drum we're not some
flamethrowers chick Paula's no two
backslashes
all right
let's get everyone maybe we'll get sixty
people and then we'll go over the new
products shop that come that I'd check
it out no beanies we have launched
t-shirts for twenty dollars now we'll
just go now let's go um so
drop up here hopefully you guys are
seeing the same shop I didn't actually
check it from an external IP but please
make this stream in 30 minutes not the
streams right now you can watch it on to
replay but so first the hoodie is gone
there is no more comedy i buddy if you
got one that shit's gonna be rare and
valuable because now all you can buy is
a common AI t-shirt okay okay we heard
you we aren't a high-end fashion brand
we are a tech company we sell a company
t-shirt for a reasonable price
so actually have to do this on this
monitor because dropdowns don't work on
the other monitor so the shirt comes in
four sizes it comes in medium large
small and extra-large all the sizes are
$20 except for extra-large which is $30
so the extra-large shirts are $30 don't
worry we'll get to we'll get to the
other products that I met at the extra
larges or $30 but all the other shirts
are are $20 you have to pay the extra
large tax okay cool
those shirts take up a lot of room we do
have a fulfillment packer absolutely all
right now you know hey man you know
we're not gonna shame fatties we're just
gonna charge them $10 more it's fine
fat shaming is bad but charging $10 tax
that's good we gotta incentivize good
behavior uncle now that that's out of
the way we can get to the actual product
launches oh we got 65 people in here all
right all right all right
so the comma space add two USB and an
Ethernet port black Leon here my
midnight black e on let me just show you
how this stuff works
by that Murch bought a primer cool so
this is the midnight black eon you'll
see what actually i use a comma space
you know I'm not even lying like I use
this stuff this is a commis maze this is
the first of the three development
products you know we're interested in
making our development as accessible to
the world as possible so here's a here's
a commis maze just like the one that you
will get it adds two USB ports and an
Ethernet port to
Rhian do not plug this into your giraffe
it's not that kind of Ethernet it's
plugged into a computer a hundred
megabit Ethernet port for your e on this
side goes into the e on and this side
goes into the panda so you can continue
to use it as before you just get an
Ethernet and two more USBs perfect if
you want to add like cameras GPS is
anything you can think of now you're
about to get banned sup plugs into the e
on like that nope it doesn't work with
neo Neos are kind of retired we don't
really use Neos anymore look if you're
buying a $60 USB hub from us you
probably are the Neo kind of person
you're the young person cameras you can
do whatever you want
um I don't waste me oh yeah neo
Deathwatch I don't wish them to die but
yeah they're kind of diorite Neos are
kind of over you guys Neos are over in
the same way clip alright cool so that's
the comma space add to USB and Ethernet
port to Erie on we could just click in
here and see what I wrote allianz have
the same ip address 192 168 5.11 um be
like a common employee you can buy your
common space this is life right now on
shop comma a I everybody can go check
that out now the second of the new
products the Panda debug board use a
debug board and develop like the pros so
what we use this for you can see that I
have one here it's a good way to get
power to everything so you can power
things off of 12 volts you just take two
pandas here
and shove it in here and what we use
this for is it basically you connect one
of these to a neon you connect the other
one to a computer and then you can use
your computer to emulate a car so it
just connects these two pandas together
you can use it for you can use your
panda development you could use it
any kind of development you want $100 so
you'll see you like see the unrooted we
just read with the CEO let's reboot the
Seon and then I'll flip the switch that
like virtually starts the car they're
pretty cool or what car can you emulate
so the open palette software can emulate
a Honda Acura ILX so you can emulate
that we include a high quality 12 volt
adapter here so this is good for
emulating car Oh bro you don't have a
panda you've got to get a panda how long
will this integrated you know - there is
no eon - there is only yon you know and
get your last midnight black eon that's
an icy on man
that's an icy and you can buy your today
right here at shop comedy I we got eons
for sale right here - yeah - camp dad
kit maybe you guys want to drop down
I've told you drop downs don't work on
this monitor they work on the other
monitor so you might want to get that
midnight black get that midnight black
eon so let's see if this one's got a
boot up I don't know if it's gonna boot
up I don't know what stay my yawns all
right this is this mic this is my
personal development Aeon so every comma
employee has this stuff on their desk
has a debug board has a commis maze yeah
so you can play back your idea we're
working on open sourcing the tooling do
that that's basic
yeah that's exactly what we do with that
so we just take a this USB wires
connected to my computer down here and
that brings us to the third of the
products this is a panda Paul and what
panda paw does is it makes your panda
unbreakable so you can go in here and if
you press this button it'll always go
into boot mode no matter what you flash
it on it right so I just connect this
guy right up here and now we're in we're
in emulation mode so this is every
product that's launched all working
together this is the setup on every
comment I employees desk
here's a commis maze that's comedy bug
board those are obviously pandas this is
a white panda this is a gray panda there
is a pan to pull right there and you see
that it's connected down here in my
computer cable not included a panda paws
are very cheap throwing $20 say price a
t-shirt add a paw and make your Panda
unbreakable so we could view the Panda
paw right here berkshire panda you must
be kidding because panda unbreakable if
you have the convenient panda paw
uh now to be fair if you only making
small change to the firmware probably
like the briquette but if you want to
make big changes with confidence
get yourself a panda paw today for sale
at shop calm down AI shop kamidana yeah
i we have a car simulator and we have
replay we have both there's actually
open source car simulator in oppa violet
you just run board d with mock equals
one and we'll be releasing some
instructions on how to do all this stuff
but first we're getting the hardware out
there so everybody can buy that merch
alright so you'll see that the way this
works here's my Aeon let's give it a
second round of funding who talked about
that I'm talking about that
so wait that sounds like fake news okay
so I can just flip this switch on the
debug board and it'll basically start my
virtual car so you'll see that the power
is up here and this is a great
environment notice that green light
comes on so you know that your car is
started and now it's you know just like
starting
virtual car so how nice is that guys
this is how we do all our developments
GPS capture yeah the GPS is in the
flyback we're working on external izing
those tools over time but for now we're
open sort where we're releasing all the
hardware on chop comedy III you know
people you don't know tell me about my
second round of funding
I don't got all right so we got
panda paw we got ass maze and we got a
panda debug board small announcement
nothing too big this is mostly for
developers of course we have come AI
t-shirt by your commented a for the very
reasonable price of $20 great pandas are
coming well here's a great Panda they
are in progress coming very soon notice
it says gray on it that gray panda yeah
great pandas are coming along really
well here's a naked grape Anna
here's a what are the new pandas
shipping out oh you mean the injection
molded pandas injection molded pandas
will come out mid-february probably
whenever they get here who won the
contest all the contests all you
remember I'll talk about that later um
it would be spelled gray wrong no wheels
no gray wrong Gray's with thee
it's with thee everywhere it's with the
e we tried really hard to do we had a
company meeting where we know it's not
gray inside we fixed that Rose you fixed
that fix on that one so what I could all
get that one bottom no we fixed it brows
we fixed it all right let's see yeah our
orders coming in let me check let me
check the admin panel let's see if we're
getting orders yo we're getting orders
today shits flying off the shelf
everyone's buying t-shirts Brown went
buying a lot of t-shirts you guys invite
a lot of teachers guys we got a lot of
t-shirts we bought these in huge bulk
because we know comm AI t-shirts are the
hottest item on the Tommy I shop so get
in today
buy a t-shirt buy your space by your
debug I never stop shilling and comma
are me go out there you know no no no
Susan I was talking about starting last
my friend okay so we have $20 t-shirts
now this is typical for a tech company
and like we look at our hoodies and guys
the hoodies are nice but but is this the
a/v company or mark it's all the same
bros it's all the same ballpark and
number of Aeon sold hundreds we have
sold hundreds of eons and thousands of
pandas and by the end of this year we're
hoping to 10x both of those numbers will
be selling thousands of units and tens
of thousands of pandas these things are
flying off the shelves we can't keep
them in stock quick enough some of you
guys might know that if you bought a
panda nothing showing up yeah don't
worry we're working on it they'll be
coming you real soon real soon we'll be
getting you pandas on pause they're
shipping out right now spaces they're
shipping out right now and debug boards
they're shipping out right now if you
hadn't guessed you know what let's go to
the stockroom I'll show you guys the
kind of stock we got and then
the scope is kind of our military badges
I want to make nice comma uniforms right
like army uniforms right
um so come over to the debug we got
debug boards we get deep on boards for
days there's some debug boards right now
you can get this smooth can be your
everybody we got giraffes for days look
at all these giraffes Toyota giraffes of
the giraffes bros we got we got stuff
ready to go we got eons up here these
are V arms got plenty of yawns oh yeah
you notice how I'm not showing any
pandas in progress
so dad we didn't Hannah's listing now we
are getting some patties okay grab the
panelist have a few pandas no I actually
sent them out I think we've actually
sent out every panda in this place so
there's no more pens all right cool
thank you for joining and we will see
you next time
comma army bumper stickers and decals
you know we can't do everything
we got t-shirts we're listening to what
the people want we got t-shirts go buy
your t-shirt right now if you haven't
shopped comma dot ai go buy merch you'll
feel good thank you